莫妮卡  这真是史上最棒的感恩节大餐
Oh Monica that was the best Thanksgiving dinner ever!
太好吃了  你把我们撑死了
They're so good. I think you killed us.
我连一口都吃不下了
I couldn't possibly eat another bite.
我要吃点甜的
I need something sweet.
-有人想看电视吗  -好的
- Does anyone wanna watch TV? - Yeah, sure.
莫妮卡  你的遥控器坏了
Monica your remote doesn't work.
菲比  你得把它拿起来对准
Phoebe, you have to lift it and point.
这样啊  算了
Oh. Aw, forget it.
你们知道我们应该玩什么吗
Yeah, you know what we should all do?
我们应该来玩
We should play that game
感恩告白游戏
where everyone says one thing that they're thankful for.
我来  我要感谢今年的秋天这么美
Ooh-ooh, I! I am thankful for this beautiful fall we've been having.
说得真好  乔伊
That's sweet, Joey.
那天我在等公车
Yeah, the other day I was at the bus-stop
突然吹来一阵秋风
and this lovely fall breeze came in out of nowhere
把一个女生的裙子吹了起来
and blew this chick's skirt right up.
对了  我还要感谢丁字裤
Oh! Which reminds me, I'm also thankful for thongs.
与其说它是内裤
I mean, it's not so much an underpant
不如说是一种伟大工程
as it is a feat of engineering.
真是太不可思议了
I mean, it's amazing
料子那么少效果却那么大
how much they can do with so little material!
还会戏弄你  会让你想
And the way they play with your mind!
"有穿吗"  "没穿吗"
Is it there? Is it not there?
你知道你还在胡言乱语吗
Are you aware that you're still talking?
有没有人要感谢丁字裤以外的东西
Is anyone thankful for anything else besides a thong?
我不知道要感谢什么好
Huh, I don't know what to pick.
是离婚呢  还是感谢被赶出来
Am I more thankful for my divorce or my eviction?
哇  我还以为你会没得谢呢
Wow! See, and I didn't think you'd be able to come up with anything.
抱歉  这是最惨的一次感恩节
I'm sorry. It's just that this is the worse Thanksgiving ever.
不  我才是悲惨感恩节盟主
No-no-no!  am the king of bad Thanksgivings.
你不能挟失败的婚姻空降
You can't just swoop in here with your bad marriage
抢了我的宝座
and take that away from me.
你不会又想细说一遍
Oh, you're not gonna tell the whole story
你爸妈离婚的事吧
about how your parents got divorced again are you?
-不要讲了  -别这样嘛  我想听
- Oh God, no. - Oh, come on! I wanna hear it!
没有钱德勒扫兴就不算感恩节了
It wouldn't be Thanksgiving without Chandler bumming us out!
这跟游行一样  是一项传统
It's a tradition, like the parade.
如果游行也出柜离家
If the parade decided it was gay, moved out,
抛妻弃子的话
and abandoned its entire family.
钱德勒  亲爱的
Now Chandler dear,
爸爸和我要离婚
just because your father and I are getting a divorce
并不代表我们不爱你
it doesn't mean we don't love you.
只是代表  他上床的对像是男仆不是我
It just means he would rather sleep with the house-boy than me.
小少爷还要火鸡吗
More turkey Mr. Chandler?
你说得对  你的更惨
You're right. Yours is worse.
你是悲惨感恩节盟主
You are the king of bad Thanksgivings.
不一定  我有一次更惨
I don't know about that. I've got one that's worse.
是吗  会惨过"小少爷还要火鸡"吗
Really? Worse than, "More turkey Mr. Chandler?"
小少爷跟仆人有仇吗
Oh, did the little rich boy have a problem with the butler?
是的  我的更惨
Yes, mine's worse!
还要绷带  还要绷带
More bandages! More bandages!
能不能再给我拿一些绷带进来
Please, can I get some more bandages in here!
这个人快死了
This man is dying!
不是吧
Oh, no.
今生的才算  菲比
In this life, Phoebe.
今生是吧  好的  那钱德勒的比较惨
Oh, this life! Oh okay no, Chandler's is worse.
记得前世的事一定很酷
Man, it must be so cool remembering stuff like that!
我都没有前世的记忆
I don't have any past life memories.
当然没有  你是新生命
Of course you don't sweetie. You're brand new.
我知道莫妮卡最惨的感恩节
I know Monica's worst Thanksgiving.
-那个就别提了  -说嘛
- Oh, let's not tell this story. - Come on.
我知道  我知道
Oh no, I know! I know!
就是莫妮卡的火鸡卡在乔伊头上那次
It's the one where Joey got Monica's turkey stuck on his head!
什么  乔伊的头卡在火鸡里
What?! Joey got a turkey stuck on his head?!
其实不是那样
Hey, it's not like it sounds.
其实就是那样
It's  like it sounds.
有人吗
Hello?
是谁
菲比
Phoebe?
乔伊  出什么事了
Joey? What's going on?
我的天哪
Oh my God!
我知道  它卡住了
I know! It's stuck!!!
小心台阶  它怎么会跑到你头上的
Easy. Step. How did it get on?
我套上去想吓钱德勒
I put it on to scare Chandler!
天哪  莫妮卡一定会气死的
Oh my God! Monica's gonna totally freak out!
那就赶快帮我拿下来
Well then help me get it off!
而且这里面好臭
Plus, it smells really bad in here.
当然很臭
Well, of course it smells really bad.
你的头塞在动物的尸体里
You have your head up a dead animal.
莫妮卡回来了
Monica!
你给火鸡涂油了吗  我的天哪  我的天哪
Hey, did you get the turkey basted-Oh my God! Oh my God!
那是谁
Who is that?
乔伊啦
It's Joey.
你在做什么  以为这样很好玩吗
What-what are you doing? Is this supposed to be funny?
不是好玩  是吓人
No, it's not supposed to be funny, it's supposed to be scary.
马上给我拿掉
Well, get it off now!
拿不掉  卡住了
I can't! It-it's stuck!
我不管  我爸妈家二十个客人
Well, I don't care! That-that turkey has to feed 20 people
可不能就着你的头吃
at my parent's house and they're not gonna eat it off your head!
先别急  大家一起想办法
All right, hold on! Okay, let's just all think.
我知道了  菲比
Okay, I got it. Phoebe?
你拉  我尽量把腿撑开
All right, you pull. I'm gonna spread the legs as wide as I can.
乔伊  现在不要闹
Joey? Now is not the time!
抱歉  抱歉
Sorry! Sorry.
好了  数到三  一  二  三
Okay, count to three. 1. 2. 3!
成功了  我吓到你了  我就知道能行
It worked! I scared ya, I knew it!
大哥  我在这里
I'm over here big guy.
我知道  我吓到你了
Yeah, you are! I scared you!
你看起来真的很白痴
You did look like an idiot.
白痴的不只是我
Hey, I wasn't the only one who looked like an idiot. All right?
罗斯有一次想说冬南瓜
Remember when Ross tried to say, "Butternut squash?"
结果讲成了南冬瓜
And it came out, "Squatternut buash?"
的确一样白痴
Yeah that's the same.
是的  那就是我最惨的感恩节
That's it. That's my worse Thanksgiving.
等等  瑞秋说的不可能是那次
Oh wait! That can't be the one Rachel's talking about.
她根本不知道那件事
She didn't even know that happened.
你说的到底是哪一次
So which one was it? Which one?
我真的不想提这件事
Umm, I-I really don't want to tell this story.
讲嘛  莫妮卡  重温悲惨的回忆
Oh, come on Monica, reliving past pain
变得郁闷  是感恩节的精神所在
and getting depressed is what Thanksgiving is all about.
至少我觉得是  当然了还有印第安原住民
Y'know, for me anyway. And of course, the Indians.
听着  在座所有人
Look umm, of all people,
最不希望我提的绝对是你
you do not want me to tell this story!
什么意思
What is that supposed to mean?
莫妮卡  应该是瑞秋来了
Monica! I think Rachel's here!
我来开
I'll get it!
感恩节快乐
Happy Thanksgiving!
我不快乐  奇普和我分手了
Not for me. Chip and I broke up!
为什么  怎么了
Oh, why? Why? What happened?
我爸妈出门了
Well, you know that my parents are out of town
奇普打算要来
and Chip was going to come over...
对  你要给他  你的"花"
Yeah, yeah, and you were going give him y'know, your flower.
莫妮卡  你能不能直接说做爱
Okay, Monica, can you just call it sex?!
你那样讲让我浑身发毛
It really creeps me out when you call it that!
还有  在做的时候
Okay, and by the way, while we're at it,
男人的那里不叫"他的温柔"
a guy's thing is not called his tenderness.
相信我
Believe me!
瑞秋
Rachel.
-感恩节快乐  -你也是  亲爱的
- Happy Thanksgiving! - You too sweethart!
各位  这是钱德勒
Uh, everyone, this is Chandler!
我的室友  也是我们乐团的主唱
My roommate and lead singer of our band!
-罗斯  -这是莫妮卡
- Ross! - Oh, this is Monica.
你好  我是罗斯的妹妹
Hi, I'm Ross's little sister.
知道了
Okay.
欢迎你来  钱德勒
I'm so glad you could come Chandler,
有很多吃的  希望你饿了
we've got plenty of food so I hope you're hungry.
妈  钱德勒痛恨感恩节
Oh, mom. Mom. Chandler hates Thanksgiving
他不吃感恩节食物
and doesn't eat any Thanksgiving food.
那还真是欢迎啊
Oh, well, I'm so glad you brought him here then.
钱德勒
Umm, Chandler,
你想吃的话  我可以帮你做芝士通心粉
if you want I can make you some macaroni and cheese for dinner.
只要当年的清教徒没吃过的  我就吃
Well, as long as the pilgrims didn't eat it, I'm in.
讨厌
Damn it!
瑞秋
So uh, Rach?
你会不会觉得怪怪的
Does it, does it feel weird around here now?
自从我上大学后
Y'know since I've been away at college.
那倒不会
Oh! No, not really.
那就好
Well, that's cool.
那么...
So did...
奇普居然为了那个荡妇南茜把我甩了
I cannot believe Chip dumped me for that slut Nancy Branson.
我再也不跟他约会了
I am never going out with him again.
他再怎么求我也没用
I don't care how much he begs!
我想他不会再求你了
I think his begging days are over now
他现在有了南茜·布兰森
that he's going out with Nancy Branson.
你知道吗  我受够高中男生了
Y'know what? I've just had it with high school boys!
他们太笨了
They are just silly.
他们只是又笨又呆的小毛头
They are just silly, stupid boys!
我要开始跟男人交住
I'm going to start dating men!
朱迪  对不起
Umm, I'm sorry Judy,
我找不到你和杰克要的碗
I couldn't find that bowl that you and Jack were looking for.
叫爸爸妈妈吧  丢人现眼
Call them mom and dad you loser!
莫妮卡
Monica!
钱德勒
Hey, Chandler.
芝士通心粉好吃吗
Did you like the macaroni and cheese?
很好吃  你应该去当厨师
Oh yeah, it was great. You should be a chef.
好的
Okay.
你猜怎样
Guess what?!
南茜很放荡的传闻都是假的
All that stuff about Nancy Branson being a slut was all a rumor
所以奇普甩了她
so Chip dumped her and
他今晚想来我家
he wants to come over to my house tonight!
-太棒了  -就是啊
- Oh that's so great! - I know!
天哪  要是你和奇普晚上做了
Oh gosh, listen if you and Chip do it tonight,
你一定要把细节都告诉我
promise me you'll tell me everything.
那当然
Oh totally, totally.
其实也没什么  我们应该有做过一次
Y'know it's not that big of deal, we already kinda did it once y'know.
我知道  但是
I know, but y'know,
但这回你一定能确定
this time you're gonna definitively know whether or not you did it!
我知道
I know, I know.
奇普还保证这次
And oh, and this time Chip promised that
至少会持续一整首歌的长度
that this time it will last at least for an entire song!
我打算约瑞秋晚上出去
So I'm thinking about asking Rachel out tonight.
唱我们上周写的那首歌给她听
Y'know maybe play her that song we wrote last week.
-《忧愁的背包》  -是的
- Emotional Knapsack? - Yeah.
好极了
Right on!
不过不要拖太久
Oh! Uh, but, don't take to long okay?
我们今晚还要去试用假身分证
'Cause uh, we're gonna test out our fake ID's tonight,
对吧  克里夫德·艾维瑞兹
right Clifford Alverez.
听着  罗兰·陈
Listen, Roland Chang,
如果一切顺利  我们搞不好不会回来
if things go well, I maybe out with her all night.
兄弟  别丢下我
Dude, don't do that too me!
没关系  你可以留下来  我爸妈不会介意
All right, it's cool you can stay here. My parents won't mind.
不是说这个
No, it's not that,
我不想整晚跟你的肥猪妹妹在一起
I just don't want to be stuck here all night with your fat sister.
莫妮卡  把这些派吃完吧
Monica, why don't you finish off these pies?
冰箱塞不下了
I don't have any more room left in the fridge.
不了  谢谢
No. No, thank you!
朱迪  你成功了  她终于吃不下了
Well Judy, you did it! She's finally full!
我说你肥吗  我完全不记得了
I called you fat?! I don't even remember that!
对不起  真的
I am so sorry. I really am.
我那时候是个白痴
Come on, I was an idiot back then.
我还在"威猛乐队"的演唱会上冲上台呢
I rushed the stage at a Wham concert for crying out loud!
我不敢相信你居然说她肥
Oh, I can't believe you called her fat.
我不敢相信你居然让乔治·迈克尔赏你耳光
I can't believe you let George Michael slap you.
真的很抱歉
I am really sorry.
我太差劲了  真是对不起
That is so terrible. I am so, so sorry.
其实我说的不是那次感恩节
Actually, y'know that's not the Thanksgiving I was talking about.
就是
Yes, it was!
不是  我说的是...
No, it wasn't. It was actually the...
感恩节结束了  准备过圣诞节吧
Okay, now Thanksgiving's over, let's get ready for Christmas.
谁要去买圣诞树
Who wants to go get a Christmas tree?!
我有最可爱的圣诞节故事
Oh, no, I have the cutest Christmas story!
我们想听莫妮卡的感恩节故事
We wanna hear Monica's Thanksgiving story!
好吧  我的故事里有小矮人断成两截
Fine, all right, mine had a dwarf that got broke in half,
不过随便
but y'know whatever.
瑞秋  你妈说你又转系了
So Rachel, your mom tells me you changed your major again.
没办法
Oh, yeah, I had too.
心理学系教学楼旁边很难停车
There was never any parking by the Psychology building.
-嗨  瑞秋  -嗨
- Hi, Rachel. - Hi.
你的新鼻子真漂亮
Wow, love your new nose!
威尔森医生是个艺术家
What? Dr. Wilson's an artist!
他帮我去掉了一堆痣  你要看吗
He removed my mole cluster. Wanna see?
-我去开  -不  让我去
- I'll get it. - No, God! Please, let me!
感恩节快乐
Happy Thanksgiving!
你的发型变了好多
God, your hair sure is different!
我们刚才还在讲呢
Yeah, we were just talking about that.
我们以前真的好蠢
I can't believe how stupid we used to look.
莫妮卡呢
So uh, where's Monica?
在楼上  莫妮卡  快下来
She's upstairs. Monica! Come down!
人都到齐了  罗斯  瑞秋
Everyone's here! Ross, Rachel,
和那个痛恨感恩节的男生
and the boy who hates Thanksgiving.
你好  钱德勒
Hi, Chandler.
我的天哪
Oh my God!
怎么了
What-what's the matter?
我衣服上有脏东西吗
Is there, is there something on my dress?
你变了好多  真是太漂亮了
You just, you look so different! Terrific!
那条裙子  那个身材
That dress! That body!
-喂  -抱歉
- Dude! - Sorry!
对  莫妮卡瘦了  太好了
Yes, yes Monica is thin. It's wonderful.
但我们比较关心罗斯的新女友
But what we really want to hear about is Ross's new girlfriend.
妈  好吧  她叫卡罗尔
Oh mom! Okay, umm, her name is Carol.
她很漂亮  很聪明
And she's really pretty. And smart.
她是曲棍球和高尔夫球校队的成员
And uh, she's-she's on the lacrosse team and the golf team.
很厉害吧  她两边都行
Can you believe it? She plays for both teams!
钱德勒  晚餐时见
So Chandler, I guess I'll see you at dinner.
-喂  -抱歉
- Dude! - Sorry.
天哪  真是酷毙了
Oh-ho, my God! That was so awesome!
你完全报了一箭之仇
You totally got him back for calling you fat!
他的口水流了满地
He was just drooling all over you.
感觉一定很过瘾
That must've felt so great!
一点也不过瘾
Well it didn't!
-什么  -没错  我很漂亮
- What?! - Yeah, I mean yeah, I look great.
感觉很轻盈  心脏的毛病也没了
Yeah, I feel great and yeah, my heart is not in trouble anymore!
但我还是觉得没报到仇
Y'know I still don't feel like I got him back, y'know?
我想狠狠的羞辱他
I just want to humiliate him.
我想让他光着身体
I wanna, I want him to be like naked
再指着他大笑
and then I'm going to point at him and laugh!
好  说不定可以做到
Okay,  we may be able to do.
怎么做
How?
男人要做爱之前都会脱光衣服
Well guys tend to get naked before they're gonna have sex.
什么
What?!
我这么努力瘦这么多
I mean, I didn't work this hard and-and-and lose all this weight
可不是为了把"花"给他那种人
so that I can give my flower to someone like him!
第一  你再那样讲
Okay, first of all, if you keep calling it that,
保证没有人会要
no one's gonna ever take it.
第二  又不是要你来真的
Then, second of all you're not actually gonna have sex with him!
只是要你误导他
You're just gonna make him think that you are.
等他脱光了  我就把他赶出去
And when he's naked I can throw him out in the front yard
锁上门  让所有的邻居耻笑他
and lock the door and all the neighbors will just humiliate him!
那你就绝对报了仇
Then, you will definitely get him back!
我要怎么误导他呢
Okay, so how do I make him think I wanna have sex with him?
你这样做
Okay, oh, here's what you do.
假装什么都能让你兴奋
Just act like everything around you turns you on.
什么意思
What do you mean?
就是什么都很挑逗
Well, like anything can be sexy.
像  像这条擦碗巾
Like umm, oh-oh, like this dishtowel!
它在我脸颊上的触感好舒服
This feels sooo good against my cheek!
如果我热了  就可以拿它来吸汗
And-and if I feel a little hot, I can just dab myself with it.
或是把它放在腿边
Or I can bring it down to my side
边从手指中滑过  边跟他说话
and bring it through my fingers while I talk to him.
这个我会
I can do that!
是吗  很好  他来了  他来了
Yeah? Okay! Good, good, because he's coming. He's coming.
你好
Hey, what's up?
莫妮卡  你能不能帮我做
Monica, I was wondering if you can make me
去年那种芝士通心粉
some of that righteous mac and cheese like last year.
没问题
Umm, I'd love too!
我好喜欢芝士通心粉
Ooh, I love macaroni and cheese.
我好喜欢这个盒子放在脸颊的触感
I love-I love the way this box feels against my cheek.
好的
Okay.
老天  我好喜欢胡萝卜
Boy, I love carrots!
有时我喜欢把它们夹在手指间
Sometimes I like to put them between my fingers
像这样  然后放在腿边跟你说话
like this and-and hold them down here while I talk to you.
如果我觉得很热
Umm, and-and-and y'know if I get really hot
我喜欢拿起这把刀
umm, I-I like to pick up this knife
然后
and-and umm,
把冰凉的刀身
I-I put the cold steal
靠在身上
against umm,  my body.
你还好吗
Are you all right?
我很好  只是...
Oh yeah, of course. I'm fine it's just that-
什么情况
What we got here?
20岁男性右脚趾头被切到
Twenty year old male has got a severed toe on his right foot.
别用他的脚撞门行吗
Can you please not do that feet first?
你明知他伤在哪里
You know where his injury is!
切到脚趾  你刚才也说了
Severed toe, just you said it!
这里说刀子刺穿鞋子
It says here that the knife went right through your shoe.
当然会穿  他穿的是草鞋
Of course it did. They're made of wicker.
断趾带来了吗
Did you bring the toe?
有  在这里冰着
Oh yes! I have it right here, on ice!
放心吧年轻人  我们会缝...
Don't worry son, we'll just attach it and-
怎么了
What?! What is it?
你带了一块胡萝卜来
You brought a carrot.
什么
What?
这不是你的脚趾  这是一小块很冰的胡萝卜
This isn't your toe, this is a small, very cold piece of carrot.
你居然带的是胡萝卜
You brought a carrot?!
我的天啊  我的厨房里有一截断趾
Oh my God! There's a toe in my kitchen.
对不起  我马上回去拿
God, I'm sorry! I'll go back and get it!
来不及了  我们只能直接缝合伤口
It's too late, all we can do now is sew up the wound.
不缝脚趾头吗  我需要脚趾头
Without my toe?! I need my toe!
等一下  我很快的
Wait, no-no-no, I can go really fast!
爸  让我开你的保时捷
Dad, give me the keys to your Porsche!
想骗我的车开  没门
Oh, I'm not falling for that one!
这就是我断趾的原因吗  因为我说你肥
That's why I lost my toe?! Because I called you fat?!
我不是故意的  那是意外
I didn't mean to cut it off. It was an accident.
我就因为这样被叫了一整年的跛跛先生
That's why for an entire year people called me Sir Limps-A-Lot?!
对不起嘛
I'm sorry!
又不是一整根脚趾头
It wasn't your whole toe!
我少了趾尖
Yeah, well, I miss the tip!
趾尖最棒  趾尖有指甲
It's the best part. It has the nail.
钱德勒
Chandler.
跛跛先生  那是我想出来的
Sir Limps-A-Lot, I came up with that.
你好无聊
You're a dork.
我真不敢相信
I can't believe this.
钱德勒  我都道歉了
Chandler, I said I was sorry.
道歉也换不回我那
Yeah, well, sorry doesn't bring back the little piggy
思乡情切的小趾尖
that cried all the way home!
我讨厌感恩节
I hate this stupid day!
讨厌有关的一切  回见了
And everything about it! I'll see you later.
等等  钱德勒  过来
Oh wait, Chandler, come here
有什么我能做的吗  任何事都行
is there anything I can do? Anything?
有  让我静一静
Yeah, just leave me alone for a while.
我是鸭子呱呱呱  一天到晚都快乐
Oh-oh, I'm a duck! I go, "Quack, quack!" I'm happy all the time!
别以为这样就算了
Nice try.
等等
Wait, wait, wait!
-听着  莫妮卡  -你看
- Look, Monica... - Look!
没有用的
This is not going to work.
接下来绝对有用
I bet this will work!
你真绝  我爱你
You are so great! I love you!
-什么  -没事  我是说
- What? - Nothing! I said,
我说"你真绝"  然后就没说话了
I said "You're so great" and then I just, I just stopped talking!
你说你爱我  我真不敢相信
You said you loved me! I can't believe this!
我没说
No I didn't!
你说了
Yes, you did!
我没说
No I didn't!
你爱我
You love me!
我不爱  别再说了
No I don't! Stop it! Stop it! Stop it! Stop it!
纱布  纱布
Gauze! Gauze!
这里需要纱布
I need to get some gauze in here!
请再给我一些纱布
Can I please get some more gauze?
真是越来越扯了
This is getting ridiculous.